And make sure that you're not just drawing from the LLM's knowledge itself,
but your personal data, your personal knowledge, or your private data and private knowledge.
Then, of course, in RAG, you have more state control than an LLM.
Here's what makes a RAG agentic.
Instead of using hard-coded pipelines that say, “Do this, do this, do this, and this,”
we're going to use an agent that says, “Here is an LLM. Here is a RAG tool, and maybe here's a web search tool.”
Now, what I want you to do is take the data, get the data, and input the data,
and then be able to search the data. It uses these tools to do these tasks,
and you don't tell it to do all of it in that order. You give it the tools and it does the tasks.
Typically there are ways that you can retry queries, so it won't just be, “Oh, this broke.”
What broke in the pipeline? Why did it break?
Is this something I can retry? Is there something I can fix here?
There's more of this looping mechanism that you can implement.